We just saw that running this code doesn't do anything.
لقد رأينا للتو أن تشغيل هذا الكود لا يفعل أي شيء.
Well that's not actually true because something does happen.
حسنًا، ذلك غير صحيح فعليًا بسبب حدوث شيء ما.
A request is actually sent.
ويتم إرسال الطلب بالفعل.
We can see this if we check out the network pane.
ويمكننا ملاحظة هذا إذا تحققنا من الجزء "network".
We want to record network traffic so make sure dev tools is recording.
إننا نريد تسجيل حركة مرور الشبكة، لذا تأكدوا أن أدوات "dev" تقوم بالتسجيل.
This is red so I know it's recording.
يظهر هذا باللون الأحمر، لذا عرفتُ أنها تسجِّل.
If it's not red, then just click on it to turn the recording feature on.
وإذا لم يكن باللون الأحمر، فاضغطوا عليه لتشغيل ميزة التسجيل.
Now, if I come down here and run the request, it actually sends.
والآن، إذا انتقلت إلى هنا بالأسفل وقمت بتشغيل الطلب، فسيقوم بالإرسال حقًا.
See, here's the request.
انظروا، ها هو الطلب.
Let's stop recording for now.
لنوقف التسجيل الآن.
If I select the request we can see it's headers.
إذا قمت بتحديد الطلب، فإنه يمكننا رؤية الجزء "headers" الخاص به.
Here's the URL that we requested and the request method.
وها هو عنوان URL الذي طلبناه وطريقة الطلب.
We can also see a preview of the request and then
كما يمكننا رؤية الجزء "preview" الخاص بالطلب
the response paying contains the actual html of the response.
وبعد ذلك يحتوي الجزء "response" على html الفعلي للاستجابة.
So even though nothing happens to the page or in the code,
إذن، رغم عدم حدوث شيء للصفحة أو في الكود،
the request is actually sent.
يتم إرسال الطلب بالفعل.